const questions = [
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the most common symptom of a heart attack?",
      options: ["Nausea", "Shortness of breath", "Chest pain", "Cough"],
      correct: "Chest pain"
    },
    {
      question: "While carrying a load downhill, the forklift operator should…",
      options: ["Drive in reverse", "Drive forward", "At an angle", "None of the above"],
      correct: "Drive in reverse"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following words signals the most severe hazards?",
      options: ["Caution", "Danger", "Warning", "Notice"],
      correct: "Danger"
    },
    {
      question: "The Health and Safety at Work Act requires employers to provide what for their employees?",
      options: ["Payment for work carried out", "Tea breaks", "A safe workplace", "Transportation"],
      correct: "A safe workplace"
    },
    {
      question: "The major cause of slips and trips in the office is",
      options: ["Unsafe shoes", "Office pranks", "Carpets", "Cluttered work areas"],
      correct: "Cluttered work areas"
    },
    {
      question: "Workers operating a jackhammer do not need…",
      options: [
        "Safety glasses",
        "Safety shoes",
        "Respirator",
        "Hearing protection"
      ],
      correct: "Respirator"
    },
    {
      question: "Wedges, chisels, and draft pins are unsafe to use if they have...",
      options: [
        "Flat heads",
        " Mushroomed heads",
        "Pointed heads",
        " All of the above"
      ],
      correct: "Mushroomed heads"
    },
    {
      question: "For Oil and liquid fire, which type of fire extinguisher is best suited?",
      options: [
        "Foam",
        "Water",
        "Soda ash",
        "Dry chemical"
      ],
      correct: "Foam"
    },
    {
      question: "Where should locks and tags NOT be placed for isolation?",
      options: [
        "Breakers",
        "Control switches",
        "Valves",
        "Levers"
      ],
      correct: "Control switches"
    },
    {
      question: "Before starting a Lockout-Tagout, what should you do?",
      options: [
        "Gather all your tools",
        "Clean the equipment",
        "Know all the isolation points",
        "Brief the security personnel"
      ],
      correct: "Know all the isolation points"
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  